And I'm to this public input and unspecial personal appearance is anyone.
I am three as Consent Agenda staff is recommending I'm 4 through 7, which are claims minutes and a master ginsure on the U.S. deal in a local government,
along with grant applications that lend us filing.
If there are no questions on any of those with interfaying of those to approve the Consent Agenda,
it looks approved.
Say.
Go ball.
What's Sentai?
Johnson.
Forster.
Sholes.
Aye.
That's the kind of mystery.
I'm also included there.
I'm sorry.
It was the engagement letter with Carphone Associates.
So doing.
We're putting the consent agenda in the U.S.
It's a gentleman, but it's a little bit part of the consent agenda.
Okay.
Aye.
I made also the work order number 17.
Actually 18.
That's eight.
It's driven it on overlay.
Coring that took some 40,000.
A leash on, Sean.
Harry often.
Okay.
There you go.
This is the next case for all of our streets.
And you'll see we've got the proposed streets to corps to make sure that we've got a good
base in order to mill and overlay them.
Not if they they corps.
Any of those streets and find that the base is bad.
It will be taken off of that list.
So we have several streets, but it might not be doing all of them.
But it doesn't have good to go in and mill and overlay street that's not a bad
base because you're just going to lose it anyway.
So Alicia, would you or are these.
More call I guess schedule two or rating two streets.
These are four.
Okay.
So we hope there's a base under the house.
And it's just a payment failure.
Okay.
So these are the worst.
No.
Five's worse.
So these are the worst.
Yeah.
We know are going to have to be absolutely everything.
Okay.
But yeah.
If we can get away with another overlay on this.
And that's what we can do.
The corps can make a really stretcher of dollars.
Okay.
You've got a few of that way.
We're just concentrating.
Four's happy.
And so how close together were these corps samples being?
Normally they're spaced about 150 feet.
We're going to try to get at least two of the lock.
So the problem is we've had on other projects similar to this is the pavement.
We'll change halfway through a block.
So if you just come in and you load one in the middle of every block, it may change at the intersections.
So where we thought we had pavement.
We get to the end of the block and we don't have it anymore.
So what we don't want to happen is we mill two inches.
And we run through all the pavement and we're milling up base rock underneath it.
So you're what you're saying is you're going to guarantee probably have to do two of lock.
And it's that how you came up with the 40,000 not to exceed.
So for every block we're going to be at two a block.
Yeah, it's kind of a mix between budget and the scope of what we wanted to cover.
So you go into a block and you.
board, you find a problem right there, our deal is going to be a cheaper block, maybe we don't
do, too, maybe we'll just do, or a three, where a normal block would be.
I just don't want to do that.
So, trying to get as much of it in with the budget and then get through this whole area.
So, you get cheaper on the core, but then that means the street, it gets, it gets in the streets
on the cost of some more grass.
So, I hope we spent the $40,000 for a good shape on our board.
Okay, go ahead, Alicia.
And I do want to correct the workboard, it says $550,000, $150,000.
Okay.
So, I can want to correct that.
So, the original one said $150,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000.
Okay, I'm going to change the spacing.
We can money the budget, so we can stay with the budget.
And then after that, they will send us a report to let us know what's good and what's not good,
and we'll go where we're at on it.
And then the next thing we'll be doing is get ready to make the bid packet for the streets that are good.
So, I think kind of phrased this.
The $40,000 is adequate for you to court-test all of the schedule for streets.
It's really the streets that we've picked.
These aren't all of the full.
Okay, that's what I want to do.
These are just, these are more of the local major streets
in the routes around your schools and hospitals.
So, that's kind of how we came to taking those.
That was our goal.
Those are good.
Right.
Well, our goal on this was, like, we've got peace street.
Because if you will remember, the county has come in and meld another,
like, the northern part of it.
This would complete peace street all the way to be J-tunnel.
And then we're completing the J-tunnel.
We're just trying to, kind of, sew some things that get around
our schools get around the hospital.
So, that we get some of our major, what he calls secondary,
residential streets.
But not all, it's just want to be clear.
This is not all of the category for streets.
This is the main, the more highly traveled ones,
or the ones in the worship.
Okay.
Now, in this project, these categories,
then we'll go out to the, and we'll get to take a few.
There's plans.
So, if you milling overlay a street that has sidewalk,
you are supposed to update the ADA facilities there
to meet current guidelines.
But that also stays in line with our complaint that we did.
So, we can improve our walking traffic.
So, if we have any of those, we'll have to go back in.
You can see what ADA improvements need to be made on those streets.
So, that may kind of change priorities too, which ones we do on this first ground
out of these streets.
But I know that street park right now
is also planning on following.
that brought some of the other fours of the car?
That are less traffic, yes.
That are less traffic.
We would be working on without the cruise in Heavens.
So is that not a mill?
Is it zipper, not a mill, and all the way to Paris?
You can explain to that a lot of you.
What the zipper does is it comes in.
And it re-encorporates the asphalt that's there
into your base to help build up your base.
And then you can come in and do a chip seal,
or something that is less tossed than what
an actual overlay would be.
What the asphalt would be.
But you use that on your very residential streets.
One of the streets is Harnit.
That street is literally one block on.
It is only used by the people that are there.
It's easier than if you start finding that you've got a soft spot
and you just go in and fix that one,
and fix that part and kind of build your street.
One of the things that we've noticed
is that we're our trash trucks on our streets.
This street's really built to withstand that weight
where they're at, and we can work on building that part of it.
You're not building the whole street up and the cost of that.
And you're just bringing the asphalt back into it
to help build that base.
And when you use the zipper, the zipper, the zipper,
the zipper, the zipper, the zipper, the zipper,
you required to take a look at the ADA requirements also.
If you don't change any of your grades at the crosswalks,
it's the way it's been explained to me.
Then technically, you don't get that trigger.
So like an overlay from where you're changing grades through there.
And so you have to go back and look at your ramps again
and make sure that they're still in line.
In all the probability of any of the streets that we used to sit
for a long time, I don't even have a soft spot.
That's right.
That was one of my question is,
how did these ones that you have projected?
How many of these?
If there's not that many of these, even that has a soft spot.
So we don't have to go in and add it.
No, if there's no, we need to.
How do we need straightening the way it's going to happen?
Other.
We are doing all of these because it comes all straight through
and now, and many places it does have a soft spot.
And Alicia, this is all, this money is in the budget.
Yes, up to 40,000 is in the budget.
Other questions for Alicia or Sean?
Do we have a motion?
Make the motion.
How's second motion?
Go, call please.
My stem.
Should I?
I.
Forster?
Johnson?
I.
And not in construction manager at risk contractor approval
with magnum construction E.
You're on it?
I'd like to ask the full vote by the nine.
And I have office agenda.
Okay?
I'll be on the April 3rd of the budget.
And so if we table it, they automatically end up on that agenda.
Do you want to explain why I vote?
I vote.
Very much in action.
This is very much on me.
It's the last product project.
We're wanting to get this thing started.
It was not just possible, but I was asking.
of the nation, Georgia, and if at all possible, let's get on this agenda, let's get
done.
Some of the work with wealth of the firms that we're not able to get all the information
they needed to be able to present it to you, yet it's due on the 29th, so we should be able
to have it easily on the need on April 3rd to have you through that.
Also, the question usually comes up, because I'm the woman that ask it, does it put our rampant
in the middle of the list, if it's not in my shape of a form, or if I'm going to
have to present it.
So, it's just me pushing it, because that doesn't publicz ask me about this, I don't
want to get it done.
That's why I'm just on the hook, you can get our keys today, but definitely have it in a couple
of weeks.
Okay.
So, do we have a motion to table item nine?
You do.
And a second?
Second?
Roll call.
Johnson.
Western.
Forster.
I'm sorry, Johnson.
Shoulder.
You're out?
Yes.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Johnson.
Forster.
Shoulder.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
About that.
Let's go ahead and take item 13.
Now, which is the main contract with Cross of Construction is CMAR for Civics and Innovation
Project.
Number one.
Jeremy and Matt.
Yes.
I'm Matt.
Jeremy is not a bad man.
Okay?
You guys have this packet.
Yeah.
The long short of it, is well doing decking repair, which was in the original contract over there
in the north east corner of your gym.
We're bringing to being that there's no longer structurally second.
There's approximately two or three foot area where that being should be six inches thick.
But it's two inches thick.
The water's deteriorated that being would brought in any PWD engineer.
I looked at it.
It gave us a fix.
We've got a born new gray being, a new buttress, tear off part of the roof that's there.
We're going to add quarter inch plate, quarter inch tube steel,
root bolt everything back together, pull back together, and walk away.
It's going to take us roughly 45 days.
Also in that is an added wall that the city requested up there to front entry to finish that area.
There's a credit of $1,200 for a solid that was in the original contract that was not needed.
We're giving that money back.
The 14,950 is cross-limbs time for being here.
We're remaining contingency is 10,627.
We're crediting that back to you.
And there's a column wrap that has been requested for the new council on the court ground for 1837.
So the total cost is 576.25.
So I think our college or description of the fix sounded to me like, so we've got this
beam and it's deteriorated because of water and the fix is going to basically be to put metal
plates on each side and bolt them in to it.
So why don't we need a buttress?
Also buttress is going to be mid-span, so currently you have a buttress here and a buttress
here.
At this end, this beam is brought in and you've only got two inches sitting on it.
So it's on the end.
And the water is brought in.
So that engineer, we're putting a new one here to help collect some of that force and then
a steel at this time, and all that together is going to transfer that load over to this
and the buttress.
I'm surprised they haven't found more water damage to the leaks that we had.
So that really, we see that, we shut it all down, sort of called an engineer.
So the 42950 is for that to be done and it's going to take how long to do that, 45 days
or just do that.
Roughly 45 days, we're into that 45 days, just a little bit right now, just getting the paperwork
done, getting material lined up, and everything gets approved, we won't.
So the majority of that, is that a laborer, is that where we're getting that?
That is laborer.
I didn't want the material to break down, we used to do this to the break down.
4 or 5 days back.
I think it's one thing I've found out today on that break down is the steel is when a 1% percent.
That I'll verify.
See that?
That I will verify.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's just been the last week in an act, it's been up to 11%.
We're going to hold the number that we had in there, which is 25, 36, 16.
I'm afraid to go away any more longer.
We don't pull the traders, I'm going to keep going there.
So if you look on these two pages here, I'm going to give you the break down.
So yeah.
Labor equipment, material.
Imagine, did you say that all of the work is going to have to seize all this is done?
No, we stopped.
So if this much of the beam was bad, we did not rip that film.
Right.
We continued to rip on this film.
So we do have to take a part of that roof that started.
We've already laid down with the cuts that engineer once that much is in that frame.
So now we've got to tear off all of this to put it back.
But the other work has stopped.
The other work has stopped.
When you've found you stopped there, but then I just want to make sure.
What corner of the building wasn't?
The northeast corner.
It's okay there.
You can't see anything from the inside.
But if you start sticking a knife up in that crack there,
that knife just goes forever.
There are some pictures in your pocket that show you from the top side.
I didn't get anything of that in my...
Why is it in my pocket?
I didn't get anything.
Did it in my pocket?
Is it in the change order?
I changed order.
Okay, so change order has been done living for a while.
So that's why I called you.
Do you want my coffee?
Yeah, I do not mind.
It's like a wine.
Why is it in your pocket?
Do you get your signature?
Okay.
Yeah.
I'll use it.
Thank you.
I just can't imagine.
So...
I just don't look on yet.
A little bit of an idea.
So that's looking down.
Okay.
That should be a 16 inch toll.
Mm-hmm.
That's just a few tolls right there.
All of this, the engineer sits surgically when we move it.
So we're going to take out all the loose stuff.
And put in number two pine and some wood epoxy in there.
And glue everything back together.
So what kind of number two pine?
I mean three to number two pine.
That makes...
So...
This is basically a two-by-fold option.
And then this wood epoxy.
It's new to the market.
He said it's just amazing.
Except we use concrete epoxy all the time.
But this stuff is made to glue all of that wood together.
And just seize it all together.
Okay.
It feels to be pretty neat to stuff.
And then we'll have metal on the outside.
That will only be outside.
That will be covered by your roof.
You won't see it on the inside.
You're going to see a plate in a tube.
Yeah.
We'll paint all that white to try to make it blend in the best way.
What was that a roof leak?
Is that where the water came from?
That was a roof leak.
There has been a roof leak there.
And it passed.
That's something that Kevin has known about.
I know that.
That's ultimately where the problem started.
Yes.
Any other questions?
And that says that that says the door quest corner between Jim and the building.
So kind of a lot of that would go away.
And then we'll see if it's a visitor signal on the heights and that's not on the
A-sherry side that's between the building.
I've been saying there will be something.
It's on the northwest side.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
It's very down.
Yeah.
Any other questions?
I'll put it in here.
Yeah.
This is in the middle.
So here's our being.
Maybe we can go back and visit this in the first picture.
That's the first picture.
Okay.
So this is our being.
This right here, this is where you will walk in from your doors.
This is that buttress that is holding that knee.
This chunk of concrete that you can...
see that there's nothing right at it. It is just gone. The things grow on. This is just
a closer-up shop. This is the show you have it's here or you're able, that stuff is. So once
we get that new concrete buttress in and then we will put the plate on the inside and part of the
plate on the outside to start transferring that load and we'll remove all of this. Fill it back
into the wood epoxy in the number two pine and then finish the steel over the top. Now,
outside all you're going to see aesthetically is another buttress. On the inside where the
vent is nice and symmetrical you've got a buttress here and a buttress here and I wouldn't call
them and represent a buttress here. You're going to see a new concrete buttress. So I think it's
all going to blend well aesthetically but leaving this now it's a year ago just not going to keep
standing in the environment. Well, you gladly discovered it. Yeah, it's a six-it-nine.
Yes. We've lived the way that things constructed all of that weight is transferred down and out because
that's that one. So I obviously don't want to have to sit there.
Lot. Any other questions? So yeah, I'm 13 is to amend the contract with a change or number one.
Do we have a motion to approve? You did be need a specific amount or, you know,
seven, four, five, fifty six, fifty seven, fifty seven, two, sixty five.
About that motion. Okay. We have a second? Second. Roll call? Johnson.
All right. Question for a start. All right. Show it. All right. Thanks, man.
Thank you guys. You guys have ever had any questions about this or longer because it's a detail.
Kevin's got me set up right in there. Great. To the top end we'll go through. All right. Thank you.
Thank you. So we're going to jump back out of 11 now recommend a recommendation from the M
T.C. V. M. R. T. C. V. V. V. That's the longest acronym we've got. To allow temporary
D. V. D. V. S. from Parks Policy and then allow open home or free wheel to camp overnight and river view.
Park. Hi, Jack. What is open home or free wheel?
Open home or free wheel is a cyclist group that will be directing group 66. They will start out June 10
from up city and start making no way up through east west during route of Route 66.
And one of the stops this year is my mobile home, which is the last second to last late.
They'll actually end up in the job of Route 66 T. V. But the June 15th thing will start arriving here.
that around 9 a.m. we're looking from Newark, 550 to almost 700 bicycles, that's
coming in 7. Do you know anybody that's ever done this show?
Dad, do you know? Do you? I don't know if it goes across Iowa for you, but I don't know.
I understand the district has made its way to return before we pass, but this is absolutely me,
but I understand that he's a standard canvas of India, but that's actually actually actually to
be the same league as Oklahoma, Indiana, all of a sort of fellow boy. So I also admit this is a
week for our time, which is good. But so somehow I've been talking with the driver who was the director
of Oklahoma for a while and going out to the river of Newark a lot of times, I actually came back.
So they had the best of the weekend, 10, 10 about from the 15th at the river of Newark.
I was a few of them, I was probably saying in hotels of Virginia, but it's probably not really very much
much, but it was because of the take-and-for-profit. And we actually was a gross fund, and when I helped
house a few, we'll probably have to get 300 of the public safety tents. That's not.
Can I also admit that there have also included a lot of support vehicles that you've
followed along on the last one of our guests, yes. I mean, one company in my youth, I know a cross-eyed
was called Port Belly Ventures, and they're going to be here and they have semi-trailers that have been
converted into shafts. You're on a bicycle that have a lot of nice things to get at the campus,
you can't click that. But I'll tell you, as it has an experience cycle that's arriving into something
like we're going to be especially in the following year, 66. It's going to be a real treat for people,
and I think it's going to be one of high lines of the bike to work to be able to camp out in such a
unique park that is on resistances. And then being that close to one, it's going to be fun to dance,
and I will, I will vouch for one of those cycles that you love the day. So Chuck, we're going to have
kind of a designated area, you're thinking, yes. Kind of a map with the, but it will kind of be
the firework area of the well-play area. Yeah, there was the run and thanks to more of a cross-breaking
price to come over, it's kind of where the shark truck will be, it's far higher than there.
And it's going to be close to where the poison cross-cloud location is, as well.
Yeah, all of them are there. And, and shade will be something that's great to appreciate.
Since then, it's not going to be with them. You probably don't have to worry too much about security,
but if you talk with the chief of the process of outwashing. I mean, yeah, really, I have mentioned to
a GM about it, but I'll be able to put more in depth as we get close to the time, but maybe a few extra
pass through, so that I, it's not so much to talk with. Yeah, that's right. But yeah, we don't sure we can
look at the works I've got to do.
and protect them and everybody else involved.
And so, they'd be coming having an ingress in the team.
Basically, coming right across the issuers.
And on which could we come?
On 25, yes.
And in the looping into the upper knee, that's what the stuff is like.
Because that'll just be a wonderful way to enter the community.
And women ask how traffic control out there, too,
if you think that would be a good one.
That would be a nice one.
And then, like, we have, I think they could get over the bridge,
so if you ask them, you might consider it.
It's a little bounce right there.
Yeah, of course.
There's a local cyclist group here in town
that has a gentle more to help us out with the welcoming committees,
a couple restaurants, a part of each staff, saying, hey, happy to be these people.
So it's a good idea to do the effort.
And a lot of people are excited about it.
That was an instinct.
The food trucks typically follow these events a lot of times.
The student trucks will.
I'm not all that familiar with free will.
But what I want is 10,000.
So this is a little bit small, but still, we have 700.
And for every three riders, you probably have a person in its poor capacity.
So you're probably going to have a load of 10,000 people
that can be here overnight for that.
Most of the girls thought it was awful.
This is the summer months for them.
So they have a lot of kids.
They have a fundraiser opportunity for them as well.
So they'll have their own authentication.
10 times.
So that's good.
As the director of free will mention, the thing about food trucks following in going day and the stops.
If we said, we had no restaurants in town.
He would be of human having concerns.
I just wanted to, I mean, they should.
Well, that many numbers.
And especially, they may.
That's going to be.
Yeah.
It might be something to ask me.
This is that.
Yeah.
I mean, actually in town around 9 a.m. on the 15th.
I'll be here all day.
Well, let me cool.
I'll train for the boys and girls.
I just didn't have any local restaurants that have, you know, poor in the service.
It's very catering.
Because I actually want to set up out there.
If I have a job.
Well, the new pizza restaurants.
They're going to sit right there.
And even more.
I'm going to be.
I'll be.
I'll reach out to, you know, mostly out all of them.
I don't know.
I just think it's going to be.
I'll be.
So as somebody that concerns.
And other than what, you know, we've already expressed.
You know, I've been seeing a little bit of concern about security.
Traffic controls.
I like that.
I like the.
On the.
World rest room facilities.
Going to handle that.
Many people.
They actually have a truck.
Do they have quarter pies?
Well, it's, it's a lot of people.
Yeah.
Okay.
So do you.
Sorry.
Nope.
Sounds like they're prepared.
I thought it was a machine.
OK, any questions?
We look like an item that we need to vote on.
because we are deviating from current policy for basically the one-nine deal.
We have most to approve, make a motion to approve.
And a second.
A second.
A little call.
Porter, sir.
Good.
Question.
Jones.
Thanks, Jones.
I am 12 recommendation from the NCFA to approve the bid document for the city of Miami.
I want to promote a sport complex.
We are going to do the NCFA instead of this at the meeting last Wednesday.
We are recommended approval.
This is a little different type of project that NCFA usually has.
We are going to do the tax money for this project.
This is the honors classes that we previously discussed.
So we thought the best thing is to have you actually approve it.
Once you approve it, Matt Gray is to take care of helping us get the bid documents out of the district.
And we looked at the bid opening.
And so I just want to clarify.
I said bid document.
This is basically the plan.
These are the plans from which they are going to develop the bid.
We are not going to bid.
And then we will see the bid by the bid.
So we are just really approving the document.
Which of course we don't have already seen.
And it reflects what we have described in their previous meeting.
We are going to look at them if you want.
We have a second.
Okay.
Go call.
Johnson.
All right.
Booster.
Western.
Short.
That takes us now to write in 14 new business.
Any new business to be considered?
I am 15 staff reports are in your packet.
Staff available if there are any questions.
We have one.
Is our crash trucks broke down?
Or I think our key point is being worked on that.
Okay.
I'll just say that in a couple of weeks.
I have to say.
Yeah.
I believe it's.
What's there.
There we can.
There.
Okay.
And just the one.
Or probably just.
Actually, the L all the time.
Of course, it goes by my half a month.
Right.
Okay.
But the L is just one.
Is there a lot like that?
Okay.
So.
Mayor.
And.
Counselor.
Yes.
Chuck.
Would you like to.
Talk about what's going on this weekend with our baseball team.
That's for a big.
Yeah.
I'm.
Marshall.
Who worked on this weekend?
I'm hosting.
You triple say baseball.
I'm.
I'm saying the first one has been out of this.
10 for a long time.
As of right now.
No.
That's the.
Well.
I've got to go.
The only.
The.
You.
They.
The.
You.
on it's going to be excited.
We got H314 number, bound to 9.
That would be coming in the down flight.
We got a couple of Tulsetees left here.
Tulsetees can just, you know, what's up,
so I got a couple of Tulsetees and there's
that we're doing and that's in the CXP.
So then we actually have a local travel
ball team that's super excited just because they don't
have to travel T, but thanks for being here.
It's also, to deploy these to the halt.
So it would be a first or three issue of a gas station.
Is this only in the season for that?
Yes, yeah, there's a little...
You can turn this according to taking place, but yeah, this will be another,
another protractor, proper dozen of teams coming.
This will be the first tournament.
That's not a second, I mean, I'm going outside of the bad.
But for us to be able to put together that many teams,
maybe think it had to be a little earlier in the season.
It's just now that...
...random note that it hasn't gotten out of the paper,
...or softball tournament that we have scheduled.
There's already 32 teams just signed for it.
Very good one.
All right.
In the other...
I've got one, and I was hoping the paper would be here tonight,
but my Emma, Oklahoma, Navy Eli Hill,
if you haven't heard, was our first college wrestling
National Champion.
He transferred to Central Oklahoma,
and went undefeated this year, and he's our first.
Congratulations, Eli.
Thank you very much.
It's all right.
See, Amanda, from the occasion he's Dean,
that you're going to...
...you know, you have some things, but make sure one of those
...and codes and not date on are...
...transficent.
That's what I was going to talk about.
Absolutely.
We...what is done, that's the northwest of the South,
...that was part of the town.
162 crash loads converted into 132.28 crash tons.
Five yards or, you know, five yards of...
...or a yard waste of loads we had about five.
yard waste tons, 1.84.
And this year, we are getting a lot of tires.
You've collected 637 tires.
That's just all in one week.
I think the last time we talked about this,
everybody was asking, what's the most unusual thing.
It's going to be picked up.
I think handstands to fiberglass boats,
...that we've also posted pictures of that on our faces.
I have to say something.
But do you know, this weekly bike, why something weird?
They must have had a hole in it,
or somebody would buy that one and then grab it on the face of a nail.
I understand he has...
...I've already heard kind of informally,
...that just yesterday and long was about another 40 tons.
Then we picked up, and about 200 tires.
Yeah, we're up to a total of 100,000,000 and eight.
as a part of what we're going to do.
That's awesome.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I think what that's going to do is the mosquito popular.
Yeah.
And two of the guys stole this time.
It has a one thing that Amber did,
too, she sent to our crew.
There was a lot of the basic documents that were given.
Which are very, very positive people.
It's just going to appreciate it.
They were taken in the center.
So our crew is worked hard.
We're going to be a central specialist in the matter of this week.
Yeah.
Because then after that, it's getting a little hot.
Holds a little bit.
Hey, concrete six.
Here you go.
Awesome.
Well, we're jumping earlier.
I was telling them, I'm going to go a story about a friend of mine.
The person's stuff out of, like, eight o'clock at night.
You've got up to go to work with six-clock in the morning.
It was one thing left out of the afternoon.
I think I could have been there.
I could have been there.
Yeah.
It was like, the flea market in Kalmosh is going to be jammed back.
We don't care.
Okay.
Anything else think?
Yeah.
All right.
I don't think there's a German.
There I hear a much to a German.
Oh, you're honest.
I shouldn't have said one last thing I'm sorry.
Okay.
We are now moving pretty much moving towards the office.
So I think a lot of you have been back there.
And please cut in some time to take a look.
And we hope that this is the last time we're going to have a regular council meeting here, and we hope that we will be in our new council chamber to address this, will we perhaps have to be terrific.
We have to be bonkers today, and to be set system and videos, and to be following up on this.
Well, it would be done yet, but I think once it's done, it's done, it's done.
We're going to be proud of that.
We're going to start to set up on the current gate.
But you know, if there's somebody watching who would really like to have peace of mind in history, it gets caught.
We don't have any problems.
Do we have a second?
Second?
The whole problem.
We don't have to be nervous.